[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Shan, you've been really strong all these years.
There he is.
Hey.
I want to go to college already.
I’m just looking forward to that freedom.
Is it really freedom, or are you escaping?
What's the difference?
For me, they're both the same.
I'm not the type of guy who commits.
Let me guess, girl number 1,569.
Shan, the heartbreaker.
Someday, you'll meet your match.
Do I know you?
Oh, I’m sorry. Do you want me to remind you?
You're just a stranger to me.
And I love challenges.
You’d know, right?
Because we're the same.
Good morning.
Welcome to Yesterday’s Coffee.
Finally, there are no more monsters here.
You seem quieter today, Shan.
Is something bothering you?
I'm just thinking of my mom.
Her death anniversary is coming up soon.
You know,
I just realized how…
fast everything happened back then.
When...
When she passed.
I understand.
You're still processing what happened.
Yeah, I guess...
I guess I'm getting there.
But whenever I think about everything that happened
I still get shocked.
I was so young when all of it happened.
It was a lot to take for a young boy.
But lately, I realized that
even though Mom left early,
she didn't abandon me.
She made sure that even if she left early,
I wouldn't struggle.
You know Shan,
I'm glad you went to high school here.
At least,
I get to see you from time to time.
Don't treat me as a School Director, okay?
I’m family.
I really see my sister in you.
How have you been? How are you?
I'm feeling better now.
Uhm…
Your dad said you're not ready to face people yet,
And he doesn't want me to see you yet
while you're still grieving.
You know Shan,
I was able to see your mom before she passed.
She asked me to help process some documents.
Here they are.
I know you're probably too young to understand.
This involves your mom's properties and bank accounts.
Don't worry.
I'll tell you more about it when you're 18.
Once you turn 21,
we can start processing the transfer of these,
what your mom left under your name.
Shan.
This is your mom's last wish.
Always remember Shan,
your mom loved you so much.
Hm?
It's just bittersweet
because it really seemed like she prepared for the day
she would leave me.
When the properties Mom left were finally transferred to me,
I thought it was the best time to sort my life out.
There's a lot of fixing to do.
I want to take care of and fix the things Mom left me.
In that way… Maybe I can fix myself too.
- Hey, surprise! - Hello!
Hi, Shan!
We're here for the house tour.
- And— - Yeah.
making Hiro jealous.
It's beautiful.
We brought something for you.
Yes...
Wait,
what time is it in Florida now?
Should we call Hiro?
Nah, don't.
He's probably busy.
- It's so beautiful. - This place is so beautiful.
It's so spacious.
I already want to live here.
Finishings look expensive.
How much?
I'm not selling it, you dumbass.
I just moved in.
Wait, what about your condo in Taft?
I'm keeping it.
This one, and the one in Taft.
Both of them are from mom, so I have no plans on selling them.
- Okay. - Fine, then what about your coffee shop?
You're opening one soon, right?
Did that come from your mom too?
Let me invest.
Are you serious?
You believe in me that much that you'd invest in my coffee shop right away?
You're not even sure; it might go under, you know?
Shan, what are you saying?
It’s you we’re talking about here.
I mean, you have a good view.
You have a good vision of what you want,
And we've already tasted your pastries.
I've already tasted your coffee.
I'm sure it's gonna be a success for you.
- Yeah, yeah. - Right?
- He's right. - Don’t worry, Shan.
So, how much?
Come on!
- Let's be business partners. - You're so annoying.
Acel, Acel, tell Haze to stop being so persistent.
Haze, stop, stop.
- Stop annoying him. - Okay, okay, okay. Fine.
It's kinda crazy though,
your interests have really changed, Shan.
From parties
and sleeping around.
- Changed person. - You're focused on law school now and—
this, the business stuff.
Maybe I'm...
getting tired of that kind of lifestyle.
Really?
No.
Not completely.
It's hard to let go of something you've gotten used to.
Okay.
The Americano is good.
Bro, this toasted mallow latte,
this will be your best seller.
I can feel it.
- Really? - Mhmm. It's delicious.
Where do you get your beans, bro?
Even the Americano tastes rich.
Secret.
Nice.
How about you, ma'am?
Does the matcha meet your standards?
It's good.
But like, what's the milk?
Change it.
Okay. Noted on that.
Neil.
Bro.
Are you still looking for Yanna?
Yup. Still can't find her, but
Hiro seems desperate already.
It's really hard to find someone who doesn't want to be found.
I mean I tried asking people.
But they haven't seen her though.
But like who are her friends?
I feel like we should start there.
That girl, what’s her name… Sam.
- Can you check her— - Right!
Check her socials, check her socials. You never know, right?
Found her.
But Sam isn’t saying anything?
Looks like she’s also friends with Yanna.
Kierra?
Check the other girl’s profile.
That’s her.
Wait, you know her?
Are you friends with her?
Maybe you can contact her.
Is she your ex or something?
Is she your ex?
Or a fling?
I honestly don’t know, guys.
I honestly don’t know.
Wait!
Oh my god, she’s so your type.
Maybe you’ve dated before.
Or maybe you could date her now
and once you're close, you can ask her where Yanna is.
Bro, do it for Hiro, right?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's… - Do you agree?
I agree.
- I don’t know what— - Right.
- These are all men. - Then it’s settled.
That is so diabolical.
Use a girl?
Fix your hair, it's been like that since earlier.
Are you guys ordering or what?
The barista here is so grumpy.
Should we just leave?
Oh, sorry, you can't leave since you're already seated.
Okay then,
what do you recommend here?
I think you’ll like the...
Iced Spanish Latte.
Okay, sure. I'll trust you on this.
Just brewed coffee for me.
Iced Spanish Latte and brewed coffee.
- Yes, please. - Okay.
- By the way, - Thank you.
you need to order food too. Can't just have drinks.
See? The grumpy barista is being demanding, too.
It's okay, come on.
Should we try their pastries?
Looks delicious.
- That one. - This one.
You know, to be honest, the menu is really promising.
But I suggest
you add some savory snacks so not everything here is sweet.
Good point.
Actually, you know, earlier
someone was asking me for fries.
Maybe I should add food that's easy to eat while working or studying.
Right?
That's right. Yeah.
There's still so much I need to fix here.
It's okay.
That's how it is in the beginning, but you'll get used to it.
Wait, I just remembered.
Someone invited me to this
café business conference next week.
I can't attend but...
if you want, I'll just give you the invite.
It's at Claremont Hotel.
There you go.
Go Shan, that would be a big help to you.
Sure, please. Send me the details.
Yeah. Sure, sure.
So, is this on the house, these pastries and coffee?
Oh, you don't have to...
Of course.
- Of course, of course. - Thank you, thank you.
Of course, not.
Don't forget to tip, okay?
Oh, okay.
Thanks anyway.
I thought we were getting it for free.
Opening a café
gave me something I can put my heart and soul into.
I want to take care of that business properly.
Because it used to be her café,
it used to be her business.
It was a special place to her heart.
And I want that to be a
special place for customers too.
And how about you, Shan?
Is the café also a special place for you?
How do you feel when you're at the café?
It feels like...
Somehow, I’m alive.
Seems like the nosy guy isn’t here.
Yes!
Come on, "us" is not even a thing.
What do you mean, not a thing? Look!
Yeah, I...
A friend?
Didn't I tell you what we are?
Just a one-night stand, nothing more than that.
I hate you! You jerk!
That asshole, my god.
Can you move away? Why are you even here?
And why did you get slapped?
It's a secret.
I had a one-night stand with that girl.
And of course, as a gentleman, I did some aftercare.
I even bought her breakfast.
And then she asked me to see her here,
and then asked if we could date each other, and I said no.
I already told her before the one-night
stand that we're just friends and that's it.
And now she slapped me and walked out.
End of a tragic story.
Ah.
You deserved it.
Huh?
What now?
Deserve?
What do you expect me to say?
Okay, fine. Listen.
Let's flip the situation.
What if
after our one-night stand,
which I enjoyed, by the way,
I asked you to
go on a date with me.
What would you say?
Even without the one-night stand, I wouldn't date you.
You didn't even think about it.
Do you wanna date?
No.
Can you leave already?
I'm studying.
You're distracting me.
Oh.
So I'm distracting you now?
It wasn't a compliment.
Anyway—
Just let me be here, okay?
I mean, I have a lot of things to do also,
but I won’t bother you. I promise, okay?
What?
Nothing.
I'm just curious about what you're reading.
You’ve got lots of sticky notes.
I didn't know you were a serious student.
Interested now, are we?
Your face is as thick as that book you're holding.
What are you smiling about?
Am I giving you the butterflies?
You know,
I feel like we're at the getting-to-know stage already.
You really are crazy.
Hello, Arman, bro!
What's up?
Sorry, I can't make it to the party tonight.
I'm on a date.
Huh? Who?
What?
Okay, fine.
Wait, who are you with?
What?
Okay, fine.
All right! I’m on my way there.
Calm her down first, I’ll be there in a bit.
What the?
I gotta go. P.S. Don't miss me too much.
He’s so full of himself.
- Yo. - Hey.
Glad you're here.
Your ex-fling has been looking for you..
She's so angry. She almost broke a glass.
What did you do?
It's Andy.
Be careful.
She might throw a glass at you.
Thank you, bro.
They said you were looking for me.
You know,
I really liked you the first time I saw you in the club.
You treated me with so much care and respect.
And I thought you liked me too.
I was hoping you'd call me after that night.
But you never did. You didn't even answer my messages.
Did you block me?
Andy—
There's nothing special in what I did.
It's just bare minimum.
Bare minimum?
You kissed me, called me beautiful and held my hand.
And we were intimate.
It's just all physical intimacy. Nothing else.
Look, if you're a commitment
type of person, you go for another person who...
matches your energy.
So don't waste your time on people like me.
I hope you can find someone
who'll give you everything you need.
And obviously, it's not me.
Oh, please don't slap me.
because I already got slapped earlier, and I can't handle getting hit again.
I have no time to spare on someone like you.
Same old you.
Non-believer of love, huh?
You can finish that.
Oh.
Sorry.
Lopez!
You're here.
What's up?
How are you?
Miguel.
Big man.
Let's go.
Is that the mayor's kid?
Yup.
How do you know him?
He's just my classmate from law school.
I'm home!
How did your group project go?
Oh my god, I survived it.
Wait.
Hold on.
Hey, why do you look like that? You look sick.
No, I'm fine.
I just woke up early because I wanted to study.
Come on, get some rest.
You might actually get sick later.
No, I'm fine.
I took a nap earlier.
and I'll sleep in a bit, too.
I'm going out.
Do you want me to buy something? Food? Medicine?
- I'm good. - You okay?
- Go. - Okay.
I love you.
- Bye. - Bye!
Our house blend is a medium roast with notes of cocoa and nuts.
But if you want something stronger, I suggest go for our Italian blend.
Sure, I'll take that.
All right. Iced?
- Yes. - All right, for here, right?
Mhmm.
That would be 200 pesos.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Please wait by the side, thank you.
Good—
Are you okay?
One Iced Americano,
or if the Italian blend is stronger like you mentioned,
I’ll go with that.
I don't think you need some coffee.
It looks like sleep is what you need.
Of all the baristas I've met,
you're the only one who sticks your nose in my business.
I don't want to sleep.
Take a seat then.
I'll prepare your coffee.
How much?
Just pay later.
Miguel, please slow down.
Just tell me.
Admit it, you're cheating on me.
You're cheating on me, huh?
That's why you won't stay away from that guy.
Didn't I tell you to stay away from him?
They're my friends, they're harmless, and can you please stop—
You're such a slut! Stop fucking lying!
Stop fucking lying!
You lied to me!
I told you to stay away!
You won't stay away! Do you know why?
You know what I think?
You're fucking each other.
- You're fucking! - Miguel…
You're fucking each other!
You bitch, you're definitely gonna get it later!
Be grateful I'm driving right now.
You're gonna regret this. Stop crying!
I said, stop. You won't stop, huh?
You won't stop?
Enough!
Kierra?
Kierra.
Kierra, Kierra.
Hey, hey, you're okay.
Kierra, you’re okay. You’re okay.
Can I hold you?
I'm going to hold you, okay?
You’re safe here, okay? Listen.
Hey, you’re okay. You’re okay.
Breathe with me. Breathe with me, slowly.
You're safe here.
Kierra, you're safe here. Okay?
Okay.
Kierra.
Breathe with me.
Slowly,
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Okay, you’re good.
You’re good.
Close your eyes, Kierra. Close your eyes.
Please.
There.
Listen to my voice, you’re okay.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
That's right.
One more time, Kierra.
Breathe in, breathe out.
Yes.
You’re safe here, Kierra.
You're okay.
I’ll just get you water, okay?
I’ll be back, stay there.
Let me walk you home.
No.
I don't want to go home yet.
I don't want my cousin to see me like this.
Let's go somewhere else.
All right.
I'll take you out on a date.
Let’s go.
I can't believe you brought me here to Bataan.
Do you know my dad is from here?
Wait.
Is that why you brought me here?
Because you know my family’s from here?
Are you stalking me?
What are you saying?
I live here too.
I lived here with my
mom and my stepdad.
Why did you guys move to Manila?
I was the only one who moved.
You left them here?
It's really different when you're at the beach.
It feels so refreshing.
I feel like I can sleep soundly tonight.
I noticed...
you're having a lot of nightmares.
That night at the Claremont,
you were having nightmares, too.
Weren't you scared when you saw me like that?
No.
Everyone's fighting their own demons, Kierra.
I hope you don't mind me asking.
Have you tried seeking professional help?
Doctor Bautista.
But I stopped going.
Why?
I know they say that
healing takes me, but I'm getting impatient.
It's exhausting to think that things will get better.
Because when night comes, I still have nightmares.
I just want my old life back.
The one where I'm not scared to go out.
Where I'm not afraid to sleep.
Where...
I can laugh genuinely.
I’m sorry. I got carried away.
Those are just my thoughts.
Don't take it too seriously.
It's okay. I get you.
I know it's hard.
But I know you'll defeat your demons.
How can you be so sure?
Because who can defeat someone
who can drink 3 cups of coffee in 5 hours, right?
Excuse me.
Three cups.
I can only handle two. I still love my life, okay.
Glad to know.
Know what?
That you still love your life.
Hey, wait!
You took so long.
Hey!
Do you feel better now?
Weirdly... Yes.
It's not weird to be happy.
I feel suffocated.
It's like I can't breathe.
And when I'm outside,
I feel anxious.
I'm afraid I might bump into him.
I don't know where I can hide.
Ke!
Ke, Ke!
Why?
Ke.
What’s wrong?
- Ke… - It's so unfair, Luna.
He can have fun.
He can party without a care in the world!
It's infuriating,
like he didn't do anything wrong.
How about me?
Ke…
Ke.
How?
Why is it so easy for him?
Doesn't he have a conscience?
He doesn’t…
I'm right here, okay?
Don't cry anymore.
Thank you, ma'am.
Just wait at your table, please.
Thank you.
Ah, two—
Iced Americano?
Alex, I'll take care of this.
- Yes. - Just serve this to table two.
- I got it from here. - Okay.
Rough night?
Didn’t sleep much.
Two lattes and two corned beef pandesal.
So, no iced Americano today.
I wanna try a different drink.
You wanna try something different but you're choosing latte?
Now you're even meddling with my drink choices.
Let me make you a special drink,
to switch things up.
Fine.
Surprise me then.
Make sure it's good.
Okay.
Here’s your order, ma’am.
That is called a Sakura drink.
Iced strawberry latte made with love.
I even added extra strawberries for you.
It's your favorite, right? I remember.
Does it taste good, though?
Try it.
Why is it special?
Because...
I only made it for you.
Give me a break.
You really like it, huh?
Well, you won't find that anywhere else.
That's why you have no choice but to come back here.
You fell into my trap.
Whatever.
Yo, Neil. What's up?
Bro, where are you?
Why?
Bro, don't tell me you're ditching the party tonight.
The whole gang's gonna be there.
Sorry, bro. I'm gonna have to pass today.
Shan’s passing on a party?
You serious?
It’s nothing.
I gotta go. Have fun.
I'm driving right now.
I guess.
See you, man.
Yeah.
Just get some rest.
Looks like you've been through a lot.
Just take a good rest.
I'll be right here.
Good morning!
Hello!
Um... Hi?
Are you new here?
What are you doing?
Oh, your sandcastle is so pretty!
But why does your toy look broken?
Are you from Bataan?
I'm from here, too.
This is where my dad's from.
But we're just on vacation, about 3 days now.
What's your name? I'm Ayi.
That's my nickname.
Ayi! Let's go, time to eat.
Okay, mommy.
We have to go. See you when I see you!
See you yesterday.
Yesterday’s already in the past.
You should say, “See you soon”.
Shan!
You’ve thought about it?
- Frat? - Mhmm.
There are a lot of perks to being a fraternity brother.
What’s your problem?
Are you doing anything later?
Do you want another escape?
Where are we going?
What? Do you want more—
Shan?
I knew it, you fucker—
Long time no see.
You have a date?
Uh—
Um—